{
    "id": "769859505a2249d0958cc35b8ebe3920",
    "title": "As Well As",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b91fb8bff4ad404fb5f5f18487ea9c80",
            "title": "As Well As",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She is greedy …………………………… dishonest.",
                    "description": "As well as is similar to both...and..",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "as well as",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The cow as well as the goat ……………………….. us milk.",
                    "description": "When we connect two singular nouns with as well as, the verb is singular.",
                    "answers": [
                        "give",
                        "gives"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The thief as well as his helper ……………………………. caught.",
                    "description": "When we connect two singular nouns with as well as, the verb is singular.",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is beautiful …………………………… intelligent.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "but also",
                        "and",
                        "as well as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teachers as well as the principal …………………………….. there.",
                    "description": "When you connect a plural and a singular noun with as well as, the verb agrees with the first subject in number.",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Sam as well as his friends ……………………………. arrived.",
                    "description": "When you connect a plural and a singular noun with as well as, the verb agrees with the first subject in number.",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mira as well as Rina ……………………………… gone to the movies.",
                    "description": "When we connect two singular nouns with as well as, the verb is singular.",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Animals as well as plants …………………………….. food and water.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "need",
                        "needs"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Elephants are found in India …………………………… in Africa.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "as well as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Small plants as well as big trees ……………………………. perished in the drought.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Sonia as well as her parents ........................................ been invited.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}